University Photography Photograph Collection UA206
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
University Photography Photograph Collection
2005 -- 2006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
University Relations Division
Photography
UA206
3348 Digital Object(s)
This collection contains photographs taken by University Photography photographers of Tufts University events starting in 2005.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series. Within the first series files are organized by photoshoot. Some photoshoots are empty as further processing of files occurs. The second series contains unprocessed accessions.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains photographs taken by University Photography photographers of Tufts University events starting in 2005. Events include matriculation, commencement, partents weekend, reunion, and special honorary events. The collection also includes stock photos of the Tufts campus.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Tufts University; Matriculation; Student activities; University Relations; Student Activities -- Performing Arts; Student Activities -- Athletics; Alumni and Alumni Relations; Facilities
- Photographs, 2005 -- 2006; UA206.001; 3347 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains photographs taken by University Photography photographers of Tufts University events starting in 2005.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by University Photography job number and photographer.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Job 050318 MKO Anderson, 2005; UA206.001.001; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050318 MKO McClennen, 2005; UA206.001.002; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050319 MKO Classes, 2005; UA206.001.003; Ko, Melody
    - Continuing adult education class in Aidekman Arts Center. Photo 020, 2005-03-19; UA206.001.003.00001; Ko, Melody
      Continuing adult education class in Aidekman Arts Center.
    - Continuing adult education class in Aidekman Arts Center. Photo 021, 2005-03-19; UA206.001.003.00002; Ko, Melody
    - Continuing adult education class in Aidekman Arts Center. Photo 022, 2005-03-19; UA206.001.003.00003; Ko, Melody
    - Continuing adult education class in Aidekman Arts Center. Photo 019, 2005-03-19; UA206.001.003.00004; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050319 MKO Diez, 2005; UA206.001.004; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050319 MKO TrumanScholar, 2005; UA206.001.005; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050322 MKO Fillmore, 2005; UA206.001.006; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050322 MKO Tangredi, 2005; UA206.001.007; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050326 MKO Marathon, 2005; UA206.001.008; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 309, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00001; Ko, Melody
      The Tufts marathon team practicing.
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 221, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00002; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 167, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00003; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 084, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00004; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 065, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00005; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 048, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00006; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 026, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00007; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 022, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00008; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 320, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00009; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 272, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00010; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 150, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00011; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 059, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00012; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 250, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00013; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 099, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00014; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 050, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00015; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 295, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00016; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 268, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00017; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 259, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00018; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 275, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00019; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 145, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00020; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 041, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00021; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 019, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00022; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 025, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00023; Ko, Melody
    - The Tufts marathon team practicing. Photo 124, 2005-03-26; UA206.001.008.00024; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050329 MKO Summit, 2005; UA206.001.009; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 064, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00001; Ko, Melody
      Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Among the speakers were President Lawrence Bacow and Somerville Mayor Joseph Curtatone.
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 052, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00002; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 039, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00003; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 019, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00004; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 034, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00005; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 058, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00006; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 015, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00007; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 018, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00008; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 061, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00009; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 041, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00010; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 008, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00011; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 054, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00012; Ko, Melody
    - Somerville Economic Summit in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 033, 2005-03-29; UA206.001.009.00013; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050331 MKO Compact, 2005; UA206.001.010; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 427, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00001; Ko, Melody
      Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall.
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 408, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00002; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 376, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00003; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 373, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00004; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 354, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00005; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 344, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00006; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 320, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00007; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 281, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00008; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 276, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00009; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 257, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00010; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 252, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00011; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 249, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00012; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 212, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00013; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 164, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00014; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 146, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00015; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 100, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00016; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 078, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00017; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 211, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00018; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 415, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00019; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 279, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00020; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 256, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00021; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 206, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00022; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 200, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00023; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 178, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00024; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 110, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00025; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 042, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00026; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 063, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00027; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 409, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00028; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 392, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00029; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 372, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00030; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 349, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00031; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 314, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00032; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 312, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00033; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 284, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00034; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 266, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00035; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 243, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00036; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 230, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00037; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 228, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00038; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 181, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00039; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 163, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00040; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 104, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00041; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 061, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00042; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 428, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00043; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 379, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00044; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 350, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00045; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 319, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00046; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 287, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00047; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 269, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00048; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 229, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00049; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 205, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00050; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 189, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00051; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 152, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00052; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 072, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00053; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 391, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00054; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 381, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00055; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 367, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00056; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 321, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00057; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 313, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00058; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 248, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00059; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 227, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00060; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 099, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00061; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 032, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00062; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 233, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00063; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 220, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00064; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 207, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00065; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 105, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00066; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 089, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00067; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 034, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00068; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 380, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00069; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 327, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00070; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 280, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00071; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 253, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00072; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 404, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00073; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 316, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00074; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 273, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00075; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 232, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00076; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 062, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00077; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 387, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00078; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 369, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00079; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 340, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00080; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 244, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00081; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 240, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00082; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 213, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00083; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 175, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00084; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 103, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00085; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 384, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00086; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 368, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00087; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 364, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00088; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 342, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00089; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 296, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00090; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 272, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00091; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 247, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00092; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 231, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00093; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 208, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00094; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 177, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00095; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 174, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00096; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 102, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00097; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 076, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00098; Ko, Melody
    - Campus Compact Luncheon with guest speaker Senator Ted Kennedy in the Coolidge Room in Ballou Hall. Photo 052, 2005-03-31; UA206.001.010.00099; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050405 MKO Balbinger, 2005; UA206.001.011; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050405 MKO Campus, 2005; UA206.001.012; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050406 MKO Balbach, 2005; UA206.001.013; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050406 MKO Brown, 2005; UA206.001.014; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050406 MKO Cluggish, 2005; UA206.001.015; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050406 MKO Taliaferro, 2005; UA206.001.016; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050407 MKO Blasioli, 2005; UA206.001.017; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050410 MKO Garcia, 2005; UA206.001.018; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050412 MKO Guillama, 2005; UA206.001.019; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050412 MKO Sattler, 2005; UA206.001.020; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050412 MKO Yeraswork, 2005; UA206.001.021; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050414 MKO Baker, 2005; UA206.001.022; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050414 MKO Burman, 2005; UA206.001.023; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050414 MKO Blamini, 2005; UA206.001.024; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050414 MKO OsterSachs, 2005; UA206.001.025; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050415 MKO Lee, 2005; UA206.001.026; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050415 MKO VII, 2005; UA206.001.027; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050504 MKO BBQ, 2005; UA206.001.028; Ko, Melody